<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TLU Campus Tour</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="start_tour">Start Tour</string>
    <string name="tour_instructions">Welcome to Texas Lutheran University, where we learn boldly and live to inspire!\n\nTLU is a private, liberal arts and sciences university located in beautiful Central Texas, just between San Antonio and Austin. This area of Texas is a great place for outdoor enthusiasts, music lovers, sports fans and students who are looking for an exceptional college experience.\n\nThis app is designed to take you on a tour of the Texas Lutheran University campus. As you walk around the campus, you will see a variety of buildings and monuments. When you approach certain locations around the campus, you will be able to hear about the history and current uses of the object at that location.\n\nWe hope you enjoy your visit to Texas Lutheran University!</string>
    <string name="tour_stop_list_instructions">Select a location to view directions and location details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_locations_list">Locations List</string>
    <string name="end_tour">End Tour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="return_to_list">Return to List</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tour_stop_info">Tour Stop Info</string>
    <string name="pause_text">Pause Audio</string>
    <string name="martin_luther_statue_info">Our \"Learn Boldly. Live to Inspire\" mission is inspired by the actions of Martin Luther who was a German monk and Catholic priest and a key figure in the Protestant Reformation. Like Luther, TLU embraces the value of inquiry, critical thinking and creativity.\n\nThe foundation of a Lutheran education is to help students develop their talents and use them to fill the world\'s greatest needs. TLU students Learn Boldly and Live to Inspire just as Martin Luther did.\n\nThis statue of Martin Luther was designed by a TLU art professor and sculptor and stands at the entrance to the Beck Building where you\'ll find our Office of Admissions and Financial Aid, Business Office, Registrar and administrative offices.</string>
    <string name="att_science_info">The AT&amp;T and Moody Science complex houses our biology, chemistry and physics departments and contains a variety of classrooms and labs. Students work side-by-side with professors to do research throughout the year and into the summer.\n\nAdjacent to the AT&amp;T building is the TLU greenhouse where our greenhouse manager works with science professors and students to identify and grow native plants and also conduct experiments.</string>
    <string name="emma_frey_info">This building is known as Emma Frey and it houses offices for our Math and Computer Science professors. It also has rooms that students can reserve and use for group projects or student meetings.</string>
    <string name="tschoepe_info">Tschoepe Hall is one of the primary classroom buildings, with classes ranging from Theater to Philosophy. Tschoepe also houses our Business, Education, Kinesiology, Athletic Training, and Dramatic Media departments.\n\nIf you\'re in Tschoepe Hall talking to friends or having a Starbucks coffee at the coffee shop, you may also want to stop by and talk to our Director of International Education about Study Abroad. We have programs with over 200 universities in 54 countries, including our most popular Study Abroad program at Harlaxton College in England. Each semester, we have a TLU professor who travels with students and teaches a class at Harlaxton.</string>
    <string name="baldus_clifton_trinity_info">Our South Residence Halls are Baldus, Clifton and Trinity and they feature suite-style rooms. After you are accepted to TLU, you get to choose your housing and meal options online and also complete a questionnaire to ensure you\'re paired with the right roommate.</string>
    <string name="krost_info">The Krost and Health Sciences buildings are home to our nursing program. We offer a bachelor of science in nursing and a RN to BSN track. Our students gain hands-on clinical experience in our high-fidelity simulation lab that features life-like manikins. Students also get hands-on experience working in one of the many hospitals and clinics in Seguin and New Braunfels.</string>
    <string name="weston_ranch_info">If you\'re interested in environmental biology, you may want to check out our field and laboratory course called Biodiversity of Central Texas. The students in this class travel to nearby Weston Ranch to collect and identify plant and insect specimens. Many of the samples they collect are shared with the University of Texas at Austin as well as iNaturalist.org which is a website for environmental biologists to share their findings with other scientists.</string>
    <string name="chapel_info">TLU is a very diverse campus that welcomes people of all faiths and denominations. Our chapel services are held every Monday, Wednesday and Friday morning from 10:00 to 10:20 and end with refreshments and socializing in Streng Plaza.\n\nWe also have a campus pastor who is actively involved with campus ministry and many other student organizations and serves as a spiritual anchor for the TLU community.</string>
    <string name="campus_ministry_info">Civic engagement and service learning are central to our mission so we have a director who leads our Center for Servant Leadership. The director works with faculty and staff to develop hands-on learning experiences that allow students to interact with the community in a meaningful way. We think it\'s important to be a partner with our local community and have a role in creating opportunities and solutions for local issues.\n\nThe campus community also focuses on environmental stewardship and sustainability. We have a student organization that works with our sustainability committee, and together, they\'ve increased recycling on campus and championed a reduction in water and energy usage.</string>
    <string name="hein_info">Finding your favorite foods on campus is easy, especially if you eat at Hein Dining Hall. You\'ll find a wide variety of options and you\'ll also see a lot of locally grown fruits and vegetables from area farmers\' markets. You can also stop by the Innovation Station where you can get a specialty salad made for you while you wait.\n\nOur executive chef is Chef Ernest Servantes and he is our local celebrity. You may have seen Chef Ernest if you watch \"Chopped\" on the Food Network because he was the winner of their Grill Masters Series. He also owns his own barbeque company and competes in contests across the southwest.</string>
    <string name="centennial_info">Centennial Hall is our newest freshman residence hall. It is a three-story, 48,000-square-foot residence hall that also features classrooms, a computer lab, meeting rooms, study rooms, a game room, laundry room and lots of open areas to encourage students to get involved and get to know each other.\n\nYou\'ll often see student groups hosting barbecues and other events in the outside courtyard that is also a great gathering, eating or studying spot.</string>
    <string name="jackson_info">Jackson Auditorium is our largest event space and hosts special guests and performances each semester. We\'ve had notable speakers such as NPR\'s Michele Norris, New York Times Columnist David Brooks and Broadway performer Anthony Rapp – just to name a few.\n\nJackson is also home to campus-wide events such as Opening Convocation, Winter Commencement and Christmas Vespers and hosts all of our theatre productions, band and choir concerts, annual symposiums and lectures.</string>
    <string name="sports_complex_info">We are the Bulldogs and we offer 16 men\'s and women\'s sports as part of the prestigious Southern Collegiate Athletic Conference that includes Trinity University, Southwestern University, Austin College, Colorado College, Centenary College, University of Dallas and Schreiner University.\n\nAbout one-third of our students participate in athletics and you\'ll find most of them at the Bulldog Sports Complex or the Jones Athletic Complex. The softball, baseball and football fields are located in the Bulldog Sports Complex and the volleyball and basketball courts as well as fitness rooms, locker rooms and coaches\' offices are located in the Jones Complex.</string>
    <string name="fitness_center_info">If you like to lift weights, get on an elliptical, run on a treadmill or take advantage of free Zumba, yoga, pilates and Tabata classes, then you need to check out the TLU fitness center. This is also the place to get information about campus recreation activities such as intramurals, fitness competitions and the annual Polar Bulldog Swim which is a great stress reliever right before finals in December. </string>
    <string name="graduation_walk_info">In May you\'ll see our spring graduates process along Graduation Walk leading from the Jones Complex to the chapel lawn, where the graduation ceremony is held. Along the way, graduates bid farewell to Lucky by patting him on his nose. It\'s said that Lucky gives good luck and good fortune to every graduate who pats his nose.</string>
    <string name="asc_info">There is always a lot going on at the Alumni Student Center where you\'ll find students, faculty or staff grabbing a bite to eat at Sandella\'s or World of Wings in Lucky\'s Kennel or meeting and relaxing in the comfortable chairs in the Graf Lounge.\n\nSince the ASC is open 24 hours a day, many students use the computer lab and take advantage of the free printing services in the ASC and the library.\n\nThe ASC also houses a our veteran\'s lounge, campus post office and offices and meeting rooms for student activities, academic support, counseling services and student services offered by the Dean of Student Life and Learning\'s office.</string>
    <string name="library_info">The TLU Blumberg Library is the research hub for student projects. Students can meet and work on presentations together in the Collaboration Lab, also known as the \"Co-Lab,\" or use the large format printers to print out research posters for the annual Student Academic Symposium or a class project.\n\nThere is also plenty of help to be found in the library. Our librarians are always eager and willing to help students with research and even offer the option to \"chat with a librarian\" online. Our outstanding IT staff is also located in the library and they\'re available to help students with computer, phone or gaming system issues. We also have some classrooms in the basement and plenty of study rooms with whiteboards and AV equipment.</string>
    <string name="scheuch_info">On a beautiful Texas day, you will probably see some of our music students playing their instruments and practicing in groups outside the Schuech Fine Arts building. Inside Schuech, our music students perform in Wupperman Little Theatre or Ayers Recital Hall while visual arts students display their work in the Annetta Kraushaar Gallery. Our School of Music is accredited by the National Association of Schools of Music and hosts the many choir, band and strings concerts during the fall and spring semesters. </string>
    <string name="langner_info">Langner Hall is one of oldest buildings on campus and is home to the humanities and social sciences such as communication studies, English, history, classical languages, Greek and Hebrew studies, theology and philosophy, psychology, political science, criminal justice and women\'s studies. You\'ll also discover the Mexican-American Studies Center and the Fiedler Museum &amp; Rock Garden in Langner Hall.</string>
    <string name="alumni_plaza_info">On a game day victory or after commencement ceremonies, athletes and graduates will ring the Victory Bell here in Alumni Plaza. The bell is from the campus tower in Brenham, Texas, and was the only original piece brought to Seguin. It\'s remained here for over 100 years and serves as the historical anchor of the campus.\n\nWe hope you\'ve enjoyed your tour and we invite you to schedule a visit, attend a class, talk to our students and meet with our admissions counselors who will personally see you through the admissions and financial aid process. Good luck with your college search and remember, Go Bulldogs!</string>
    <string name="play_text">Play Audio</string>
    <string name="title_activity_direction_map">Map</string>
    <string name="settings_updated">Settings Updated</string>
    <string name="location_conn_error">Could Not Connect to Location Services</string>
    <string name="tour_stops_list_title">Tour Stops</string>
    <string name="directions_title_start">"Directions to "</string>
    <string name="map_options_title">Map Options</string>
    <string name="map_loading_message">Please Wait for the Map to Load</string>
    <string name="my_location_marker_title">My Location</string>
    <string name="directions_conn_error">Directions Not Available</string>
    <string name="spanish_option">Spanish</string>
    <string name="english_option">English</string>
    <string name="language_options">Language Options</string>
    <string name="driving_option">Driving Directions</string>
    <string name="walking_option">Walking Directions</string>
    <string name="transportation_options">Mode of Transportation</string>
    <string name="satellite_option">Satellite View</string>
    <string name="normal_option">Normal View</string>
    <string name="map_view_options">Map View</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="accessibility_options">Accessibility Options</string>
    <string name="use_handicap_entrances">Use Handicap Entrances</string>
</resources>
