<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TLU Campus Tour</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="start_tour">Start Tour</string>
    <string name="tour_instructions">Welcome to Texas Lutheran University, where we learn boldly and live to inspire!\n\nThis app is designed to take you on a tour of the Texas Lutheran University campus. As you walk around the campus, you will see a variety of buildings and monuments. When you approach certain locations around the campus, you will be able to hear about the history and current uses of the object at that location.\n\nTLU is a private, liberal arts and sciences university located in beautiful Central Texas, just between San Antonio and Austin. This area of Texas is a great place for outdoor enthusiasts, music lovers, sports fans and students who are looking for an exceptional college experience.\n\nWe hope you enjoy your visit to Texas Lutheran University!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_locations_list">LocationsList</string>
    <string name="end_tour">End Tour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="return_to_list">Return to List</string>
    <string name="arrived_test">I\'m Here</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tour_stop_info">TourStopInfo</string>
    <string name="pause_text">Pause Audio</string>
    <string name="martin_luther_statue_info">Our "Learn Boldly. Live to Inspire" mission is inspired by the actions of Martin Luther who was a German monk and Catholic priest and a key figure in the Protestant Reformation. Like Luther, TLU embraces the value of inquiry, critical thinking and creativity.\n\nThe foundation of a Lutheran education is to help students develop their talents and use them to fill the world\'s greatest needs. TLU students Learn Boldly and Live to Inspire just as Martin Luther did.\n\nThis statue of Martin Luther was designed by a TLU art professor and sculptor and stands at the entrance to the Beck Building where you\'ll find our Office of Admissions and Financial Aid, Business Office, Registrar and administrative offices.</string>
    <string name="att_science_info">The AT&amp;T and Moody Science complex houses our biology, chemistry and physics departments and contains a variety of classrooms and labs. Students work side-by-side with professors to do research throughout the year and into the summer.\n\nAdjacent to the AT&amp;T building is the TLU greenhouse where our greenhouse manager works with science professors and students to identify and grow native plants and also conduct experiments.</string>
    <string name="tschoepe_info">Tschoepe Hall is one of the primary classroom buildings, with classes ranging from Theater to Philosophy. Tschoepe also houses our Business, Education, Kinesiology, Athletic Training, and Dramatic Media departments. If you\'re in Tschoepe Hall talking to friends or having a Starbucks coffee at the coffee shop, you may also want to stop by and talk to our Director of International Education about Study Abroad. We have programs with over 200 universities in 54 countries, including our most popular Study Abroad program at Harlaxton College in England. Each semester, we have a TLU professor who travels with students and teaches a class at Harlaxton.</string>
    <string name="play_text">Play Audio</string>
</resources>
